# Shweta Singh () Featured

Senior IT professional with 11+ years of industry experience seeking roles in ModelN/Revitas Application Support, Software Development, Application Programming, Application Support, ITSM, Incident Management, PL/SQL, C#.Net, ASP.Net, VB.NET, Unix



Current Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Total Experience: 11 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: modeln/revitas application support, application programming, web development, application support, production support, pl/sql, asp.net, vb.net, unix, itsm, incident management, documentation, agile methodology,it

skills,c#,Query Optimization

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 18-Jan-21 Last Modified: 18-Jan-21

## Summary

A highly motivated and focussed software engineer with 11+ years of experience in the IT industry, that includes a 3 years (2016 to 2019) onsite stint in the US, working closely with the clients as a techno-functional consultant

Skilled in all phases of the software development lifecycle, expert at delivering quality solutions by paying close attention to detail throughout the process, even in high pressure situations. A good team player with strong analytical, problem solving, leadership and communication skills.

## **Work Experience**

TCS as Assistant Consultant Oct 2015 to Feb 2020

**Tata Consultancy Services** as IT Analyst Oct 2012 to Oct 2015

**Tata Consultancy Services** as Systems Engineer Nov 2010 to Oct 2012

**CYGNET INFOTECH PRIVATE LIMITED** as Software Engineer Mar 2009 to Nov 2010

**KALPTARU INFOSOFT PRIVATE LIMITED** as Software Developer Aug 2008 to Dec 2008

#### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from HEMCHANDRACHARYA NORTH GUJARAT UNIVERSITY, PATAN in 2008

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Software Estimation

#### **IT Skills**

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
PL/SQL		2020	11 Year(s)
COGNOS BI		2020	1 Year(s)
Unix		2019	2 Year(s)
Agile Methodology		2020	6 Year(s)
ASP.NET, C#.NET, VB.NET		2016	5 Year(s)
Visual Basic		2013	1 Year(s)
Delphi		2012	4 Year(s)

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Gujarati				
Bengali				

### **Affirmative Action**

Physically Challenged: No

### **Work Authorization**

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time